getgoogleadsfree.com 2008-06-22

# 

**WebBusinessSecrets.com LLC. (“WBSLLC”) Online Privacy Policy (Last updated March 25, 2007)**

WBSLLC has established this Privacy Policy to explain how it protects and manages the personal information that it collects from you (the customer) online. 

**1.** **Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure**

Your use of this or any other WBSLLC site(s) and/or your registration for WBSLLC product(s) and service(s) constitute(s) your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the WBSLLC site.

WBSLLC may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When it does, WBSLLC will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. In addition, WBSLLC may not necessarily seek a customer’s prior consent, by email, for any new uses or proposed disclosures of information collected from the customer prior to the change. WBSLLC may not necessarily notify customers by email of changes to this policy that will affect information collected from them in the future.

In certain circumstances, WBSLLC will not inform and obtain the consent of the customer, such as in connection with an investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, the collection of a debt or in compliance with the request of a law enforcement agency or a court order. And your use of this or any other WBSLLC website(s) constitutes your permission to do so on our part, and at any time.

A customer may withdraw his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by opting out of our mailing list by simply clicking on the appropriate link found in the very bottom of any email/newsletter issue; and which satisfies at the very minimum required in accordance with the latest revision of the CAN-SPAM Act.

Please note that, if you do, WBSLLC may suspend its provision of any further products and services to you. When you unsubscribe, if you fall within the window of opportunity in which to request either a return for a product or its replace or repair, the discretion rests entirely on ClickBank to decide what action to take, and NOT WBSLLC.

**2.** **Accountability**

WBSLLC collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to its website, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) including but not limited to your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number, and information about your computer hardware and software (e.g., IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring website addresses).

WBSLLC has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect personal information received from its customers, and to respond to any inquiries. The Privacy Policy also provides that WBSLLC will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties on WBSLLC’s behalf; including but not necessarily limited to ClickBank.

WBSLLC has designated responsibility for your personal information to its Privacy Officer, who ensures compliance with the principles in this Privacy Policy. Other WBSLLC individuals may be delegated to act on behalf of the Privacy Officer.

**3.** **Purposes for Collecting Personal Information**

WBSLLC collects and uses personal information for the following Identified Purposes:

(a) to understand customer needs regarding WBSLLC’s services;

(b) to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our customers;

(c) to fulfill your requests for products, services or information;

(d) to communicate with customers and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform customers of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from WBSLLC, its affiliates and third parties;

(e) to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of WBSLLC’s site(s);

(f) to personalize some of our services and products for you and to deliver targeted advertisements and offers from WBSLLC and at times we deem appropriate third parties;

(g) to bill accounts and maintain payment records;

(h) to comply with any applicable law(s), regulation(s), legal process(es) or government request(s);

(i) to respond to a legitimate claim(s), or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreement(s) or policy(ies) that govern your use of the WBSLLC site(s) or any WBSLLC product(s) or service(s);

(j) to protect the service(s), product(s) or rights of WBSLLC, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the WBSLLC site(s); and

(k) to identify and resolve any technical problem(s) concerning WBSLLC’s site(s), and any product(s) and service(s).

WBSLLC also uses personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.

If we hire other companies to provide some product(s) or service(s) on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the Identified Purposes, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your personal information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.

**4.** **Limiting the Collection of Personal Information**

WBSLLC limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes. WBSLLC does not direct its site to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

When you visit the WBSLLC website(s), a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the WBSLLC site previously.

WBSLLC uses cookies, and ClickBank does also with any WBSLLC/ClickBank-partnered website(s), and to allow WBSLLC to determine which product(s) and service(s) you have already purchased so that WBSLLC does not provide redundant information to you, and, if you are a WBSLLC affiliate, to track WBSLLC sales made to customers referred by you so that you can receive compensation under our affiliate program.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the WBSLLC website(s), you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalised visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the WBSLLC site(s).

**5.** **Disclosure, Processing and Retention**

WBSLLC does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:

(a) to someone you have designated to act as your agent, for one or more of the Identified Purposes (listed in Section 2, above);

(b) to WBSLLC’s employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on WBSLLC’s behalf for any of the Identified Purposes;

(c) as necessary if WBSLLC has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with WBSLLC’s rights or property, other users of WBSLLC’s web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and

(d) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.

In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that WBSLLC or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which WBSLLC or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this website, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

After your account becomes inactive (that is, if you request to be removed from our database), WBSLLC will keep your personal information in its archives. Your information will then be used only as necessary for tax reasons or to prove WBSLLC’s compliance with any applicable law(s).

**6.** **Accuracy of Personal Information**

WBSLLC will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information.

Customers are responsible for informing WBSLLC about changes to their personal information. You can do this simply by re-subscribing using a new email address and submit your newer contact details as you did before and originally upon signing up; and also you may further help us so as not to create additional obsolete account information by simultaneously un-subscribing using any email issue sent prior to your new information, and using the appropriate un-subscribe link located in the bottom of same.

WBSLLC will use new or updated personal information it receives from customers to update its own records. 

**7.** **Security Safeguards**

WBSLLC will use reasonable efforts to protect customers’ personal information; but you accept that some things exceed WBSLLC’s ability(ies) to do so effectively, as well as unforeseen or even possibly unknown events, activities, occurrences, etc.

**8.** **Access to Personal Information**

WBSLLC will afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file, if you so request by sending a **certified letter, return receipt requested** ONLY to:

**WebBusinessSecrets.com LLC**  
676A 9th Avenue, Ste 215   
New York, NY 10036   
USA

If WBSLLC is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer’s personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as:

  * that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, 
  * or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney–client privileged   
communications, 
  * or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, 
  * or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of   
another individual.

Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, by contacting WBSLLC as described above. WBSLLC will promptly correct such personal information, as long as it’s within its means to do so.
